# Keli Elizabeth Rice

I am a Creative Designer with an educational and professional background that spans architecture, user experience design, and human-computer interaction design in complex technical environments. My favorite design problems exist where technology meets space, and my diverse background helps me bridge the gaps that my clients often encounter.

# Experience

2024-PRESENT

Technology Systems Designer

Hammel, Green, and Abrahamson (HGA)

Experience Consultations | Technology Design
Developing AV Models and Drawings | Process Development
AV Drawings and System Review | Cost Evaluation

2017-2024

Director of UX/UI Design

**Professional Audio Design** 

UI Designer for AV Systems | Front-End Development
User Training | Establishing UX Design Processes
Brand Stewardship | System Evaluation and Labor Estimates

2014-2017

Architectural Assistant

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee

Project Manager for Campus Signage | Graphic Design Manage Campus Planning Website | Promote Capital Projects Maintain Facility Database | Event Coordination

## Interests

User Centered Design | Collaborative Project Approach | User Training Interaction Design | Rapid Prototyping | Information Sciences

Cross Directional Mentorship | Diagramming and Iterative Design

Electronic Exhibits | Rock Climbing | Cycling | Community Science

## Education

#### BS Architecture - University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee

Two-Dimensional Design | Greening Milwaukee | Architecture & Human Behavior | Virtual Modeling | Sustainable Architecture of the 21st Century

#### CONTACT ME

kelirice.com hello@kelirice.com linkedin.com/in/kelirice instagram.com/ktrocity/

#### MY WORK

Dodge Performing Arts Center St. Mary's College of Maryland

Milwaukee Symphony Orchestra Bradley Symphony Center

PRAx Center for Creative Arts
Oregon State University

Corporate Headquarters **Duluth Trading Company** 

Various Hearing Rooms
Wisconsin State Capitol

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

InDesign, Illustrator, Figma Rhino, Revit, AutoCAD Clip Studio, Photoshop VS Code, GitHub

#### CERTIFIED STUDY

AV Mathematics (AVIXA)

UX Design (Coursera)

QSYS Level I (QSC)

Dante Level III (Audinate)